<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cold War Barracks</string>

    <string name="AK47">Full-auto assault rifle. High damage with a marginally slower fire rate. Excellent stopping power for mid to short range encounters.</string>
    <string name="Krig6">Full-auto assault rifle. Improved damage and accuracy. Excellent weapon control and visibility when sustaining fire.</string>
    <string name="XM4">Full-auto assault rifle. Reliable damage with improved fire rate. Fair weapon control when sustaining fire.</string>
    <string name="QBZ83">Full-auto assault rifle. Superiror mobility with improved handling speeds. Erratic initial recoil with less accurate hipfire spread.</string>

    <string name="AK74u">Full-auto submachine gun. Improved damage with reliable weapon control. Utilizes 5.56mm ammo for superior penetration.</string>
    <string name="Milano_821">Full-auto submachine gun. High damage with a slower fire rate and fair recoil. Improved handling speeds with more accurate hipfire spread.</string>
    <string name="MP5">Full-auto submachine gun. Fast fire rate with low recoil. Good visibility and control while firing.</string>
    <string name="KSP_45">3-round burst submachine gun. High damage with moderate range. Burst fire spread is less efficient at long range.</string>

    <string name="M16">Burst fire tactical rifle. Excellent burst fire accuracy when aiming down sights. Good visibility while firing, with a slightly pronounced delay between bursts.</string>
    <string name="Type_63">Semi-auto tactical rifle. High damage and reliable accuracy with lower ammo capacity. Fair visibility and control while firing.</string>

    <string name="RPD">Full-auto light machine gun. Improved handling speeds with more accurate hipfire spread. Less ammo capacity and heavier recoil when sustaining fire.</string>
    <string name="Stoner_63">Full-auto light machine gun. Improved fire rate with a large ammo capacity. Good recoil control and visibility when sustaining fire.</string>

    <string name="Pelingtong703">Bolt-action sniper rifle. Hand loaded with improved handling speeds and faster rechamber. 1-shot kill to the head or chest.</string>
    <string name="LW3_Tundra">Bolt-action sniper rifle. High damage with moderate sway, 1-shot kill to the head, chest or shoulders.</string>


    <string name="pistol1911">Semi-auto pistol. Good accuracy with a modest ammo capacity. High damage in close range encounters.</string>
    <string name="Diamatti">Burst fire pistol. Fast cyclic rate of fire with a short delay between bursts. Increased ammo capacity and slightly slower reloading speeds.</string>
    <string name="Magnum">Double action revolver. High damage with increased penetration and lower muzzle velocity.</string>

    <string name="Hauer77">Pump-action shotgun. High damage with a possible 1-shot kill in close quarters. Hand loaded with moderate rechamber speed.</string>
    <string name="GalloSA12">Semi-auto shotgun. Reliable damage and pellet spread. Heavy recoil and low visibility when sustaining fire.</string>

    <string name="Cigma2">Free-fire rocket launcher. Lock-on capability vs enemy vehicles. Locked rockets travel faster to their targets and maneuver in flight.</string>
    <string name="RPG7">Free-fire rocket launcher. Increased blast radius with heavy damage to vehicles, equipment, and personnel. Additional rockets provided.</string>

    <string name="Knife">Lethal melee weapon. Straight-edge blade that kills enemies with a single deadly strike.</string>

</resources>